"4 Years Ago"
Ah, thanks for always...
"Super delicious! The next generation” "Water Dispenser”
"The ultimate natural spring water to keep you healthy”
"Call time" "The secret to successful
walk-in sales is a smile!!I"
"Call time" "The secret to successful walk-in sales
is a smile!!I" Thank you for your continued business!
Thank you for your continued business!
Is that so? We'll make
arrangements right away!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no!
It's all thanks to you!
Yes.
"Clincity Inc.”
I'll take it.
Thank you so much!
"Saturdays only Just 2 hours in the morning!!” "Working
with a fun staff daily to make every day exciting!!”
"Working at a sushi shop! Just packing sushi into containers or working the
register!!” "A location in front of the station is opening this month!!"”
"Working at a sushi shop! Just packing sushi into containers or working the register!!” "A
location in front of the station is opening this month!!"” ]I wonder what I should do now.
I wonder what I should do now.
"I got 20,000 just for getting hired! My hourly wage went up a lot, too." "A hole-in-the-wall place for adults.
A place with a homey atmosphere with plenty of other fellow part-timers!” ]I wonder what I should do now.
I ended up renting this place
without having anything lined up.
"Power Stone" "You can
become a millionaire, too!!"
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
Can't you feel your own frustration?
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions
on your sleeve and break it down
What do you see once you go
beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9)
The mysterious percentage
Cr yin' my life, or yin' my psyche,
Cr yin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal?
Is that your mind? Right now
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR OWN.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
"Poor, Lonely, Whitey"
"Telepathy Club" "Body
Improvement Club" Thirty-one...
Thirty-one...
Thirty-two...
Thirty-three...
Thirty-four...
Thirty-five...
You did it! That's a new record!
You've gotten stronger, Kageyama!
--Your muscles are evolving!
--Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
--All your efforts are finally paying off!
"Body improvement!!” --All your efforts are finally paying off!
--Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
"Body
improvement!!"
"Body improvement!!" I thought
his workouts were a waste of time...
I thought his workouts were a waste of time...
...but the way he's improving step by step
will make him more confident as well.
He even looks bolder.
"Potato Demons"
"Potato
Demons"
“"Potato Demons” Mob-kun's
having fun, being tossed in the air.
"Potato
Demons"
"Potato Demons" Oh, I know!
"Potato
Demons"
"Potato Demons" Why
don't you toss him, too?
"Potato
Demons"
"Potato Demons"
It's his birthday today.
"Potato
Demons"
Huh? No, that's okay.
Is it your birthday, Kijibayashi?
Y-Yeah...
--Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
--What a joyous day! Let us celebrate!
--Oh, hey, President.
--Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
--It was my birthday last week, too.
What? It was?!
Then why don't we throw a birthday party?
How about we all go to a family restaurant?
What a nice idea, Saruta!
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
What's this?
It's extremely rare rock salt obtained
from the Uyuni Salt Flats,
and it's excellent for exorcisms!
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello, this is the Spirits and
Such Consultation Office.
What? Frozen tofu spirits?
Of course I've heard of them!
Leave it to me.
I'm getting one job after another lately...
"Guspo Restaurant” Happy birthday,
happy birthday, Kijibayashi and Kumakawa!
» Happy birthday, happy birthday,
Kijibayashi and Kumakawa! )
happy birthday to you! )
We got the drink bar,
so let's drink until we've had our fill!
I never thought you'd stick with the Body
Improvement Club for so long, Mob-kun.
I thought he'd run away immediately.
Kageyama's pretty persistent.
Do you have some huge goal
you want to accomplish?
If you keep at it for another six months,
I think you'll reach the level of an
average second-year middle schooler.
Nah.
I'm sure Kageyama has his sights set
on a much loftier goal.
If we let our guards down,
he might surpass us before we know it!
All he wants is for the girl he likes
to look his way, really.
That was it at first, but now...
By the way, Mob-kun,
I hope you haven't forgotten.
You're supposed to help me
find other telepaths.
Oh. You're still looking for them?
Of course I am! What do you think
the point of the Telepathy Club is?!
--More importantly, why don't
we all go to karaoke?
--"More importantly"?!
--More importantly, why don't we all go to karaoke?
--More importantly, why don't
we all go to karaoke?
Huh? Karaoke?
What? You've never gone before?
Let's go, then. A chance like this
won't come along very often.
Well, if you insist...
What should I sing?
Feeling shy, Mob?
You'll be fine once you start singing.
No, I was just thinking it's been a while
since I've done something like this.
Just hanging out with people.
I-It's so much fun...
"Incoming call"
"Master Reigen”
--Hello?
--Oh, hey, Mob.
There's an evil spirit
giving me some trouble.
I mean, I could totally deal with it myself,
but there's been so much work lately.
I'd rather not use too much of my power...
Mob?
Master, could you handle
things on your own today?
Huh?
I-I've asked you many times before
not to summon me on such short notice.
What are you talking about?
I bet you're free, anyway.
Is there a reason you can't show up?
There's a client who really
needs your help here.
I'll be waiting for you,
so try not to take too long.
What's the matter, Kageyama?
Must be that shady-ass master of yours again.
A sudden job came in,
so I won't be able to go to karaoke.
I'm really sorry for missing out
on your birthdays.
Oh, don't worry about us.
Yeah, you've done plenty.
Some things take priority over others.
It's okay. We understand.
The ghost of a man who hit his head
on a block of frozen tofu and died?
That rumor was true?
How about I make you think of me
every time you see a block of tofu?!
Please, hurry up and exorcise him!
Have no fear.
I have my disciple heading over immediately.
You're a lifesaver, Mob.
What's wrong?
Even I have school and a private life.
So please, stop summoning me out of the blue.
A private life? Just working out
in that club of yours, right?
Or did you fall for another
person jokingly asking you out?
You get taken advantage of so easily.
Grow up, for crying out loud.
I don't know what you were doing
with your schoolmates,
but do they really understand you?
Come on, we're saving lives here!
You're making a difference
in the world by helping me out!
Not to mention, I'm your master!
I'm one of the biggest reasons
you're able to control your powers!
Listen up...
Choose your social circle wisely, Mob!
If they're going to get in the way of
your exorcism job, get rid of them!
They don't actually care about you.
They're just having fun
mocking someone as wimpy as you--
That's not true!
I-I might've said too much there...
They aren't mocking me.
R-Right...
I'm starting to understand that not
everything you say is true, Master.
"Dug his own grave"
Shit. I messed up...
C-Come on now, Mob! You must be tired!
Let's get some ramen on the way back.
I'm not being mocked,
nor am I easily taken advantage of.
"Reception" "The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Reception" "The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka's
Spirits and Such Consultation Office" Damn it, Mob...
"Reception" "The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
I'd promised this client in advance...
He finally decided not to show up.
I guess I really did say too much yesterday.
But then again...
He shouldn't have anyone he can talk
to about his problems other than me.
If he cuts ties with me,
he's going to end up alone again.
There's nothing to worry about.
He'll be back here. I know it.
Huh? Nii-san?
You're home early today.
Welcome home, Ritsu.
I've decided not to go to
Master's place for a while.
That's fine and all,
but what brought this on?
They had a fight. He cut ties with him.
That's not it. But I gave it a lot of
thought and made my decision.
I've been blindly following what
Master Reigen says way too often.
I felt like things went better that way,
so it was easier for me.
But...
Grow up, for crying out loud.
I realized that I can't just
keep relying on him,
so I thought I'd reconsider
what I want to do a bit more.
Wanna play some video games for once?
Too bad, Reigen.
It's your own fault for messing up.
I feel like I've sweat off
whatever was lurking over me.
Coral steam yoga is the best.
Glad to hear it.
Thank goodness it wasn't a real spirit.
"4 Years Ago"
Why am I so surprised, though?
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" I basically
built this business from the ground up all by myself.
I basically built this business
from the ground up all by myself.
"Option A -- Trial Course"” "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B -- Serious Course” "A Mere 5,000 yen" "Option C
-- All-Out Course"” "A Mere 12,000 yen" I basically built this business from the ground up all by myself.
I basically built this business
from the ground up all by myself.
Why would I be in any trouble
if Mob decides to not show up?
I just need to continue focusing
on the jobs I can do by myself.
I can let the real psychics
deal with actual spirits.
Yeah! Now I can reduce labor costs,
and I won't have to hear
about his teenage dilemmas.
I only have so much time in a day.
I should use it to study
and learn more about the world.
Hey, I'm becoming rather
optimistic about this.
Sorry, Mob. You probably
weren't expecting this,
but I'm not sad about this at all.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" I'm sure
you're probably feeling pretty lonely right about now.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
"Salt"
I'm sure Mob's really regretting this by now.
Maybe he feels awkward about talking to me.
I'm mature enough to understand,
so it's not like I'd even care.
"Super popular!!"
Impossible! Mob looks like
he's actually having fun!
He actually had friends?!
What the hell are you hiding for, dumb-ass?
"Yosokaze!"
Dimple!
I-I'm not hiding at all!
"Yosokaze!"
You don't need to worry about Mob anymore.
He's having fun.
"Yosokaze!"
"Yosokaze!" Well, too bad
I'm not actually worried at all!
Well, too bad I'm not
actually worried at all!
Good to hear.
Shigeo doesn't seem to be
concerned about you at all.
It's rather peaceful.
What?!
Are you okay with this, Dimple?
What do you mean?
The more he stays away from me,
the less he'll use his powers.
Do you want to be an ordinary
middle schooler's pet forever?
Guess that would be pretty peaceful.
I think you wanted to use Mob's powers
to do something, but sucks to be you.
Now that Mob's decided to
lead such a mundane life,
he's of no use to anybody!
I hope you have fun following
around a normal middle schooler.
I, on the other hand,
will be moving on to the next stage!
Well, I'm glad to see
you're doing all right.
If you can crack jokes like that,
I guess there's no need to worry.
Who knows? We may never
see each other again.
Guess I'll update the homepage.
"Karaoke"
Huh? Aren't we going home?
Weren't we giving up
looking for telepaths today?
You couldn't go the other day
because of work, right?
We're here anyway, so let's go.
"Karaoke"
"Karaoke" You'll be able to sense
a telepath if they're nearby, right?
"Karaoke"
Then you can do it while you're singing, too.
But wait! I'm not mentally prepared!
"Karaoke"
Oh, come on. Get in there.
"Newbie Idol's Blog Gets Flamed"
A newbie idol's blog got flamed, huh?
I guess I haven't checked
Friendbook in a while.
In this day and age, you can connect
with the people you know at any time.
Talk about convenient.
Hey, I have a message!
Sorry for not reading it sooner.
I've just been so busy.
"Search" “"Archive I Settings” Sorry for not
reading it sooner. I've just been so busy.
"Search"
"Archive I Settings”
"Search" " Archive I Settings" Who could it be?
Maybe it's that one person from high school...
Who could it be? Maybe it's
that one person from high school...
"Congratulations! It's your birthday today.” "Upload a photo or video, or post
something” Who could it be? Maybe it's that one person from high school...
"Congratulations! It's your birthday today."
"Upload a photo or video, or post something"”
Oh, right...
I totally forgot.
"Congratulations! It's your birthday today."
"Upload a photo or video, or post something"
"Congratulations! It's your birthday today.” "See messages
from your friends wishing you a happy birthday (O messages)”
Seriously?
Huh? A message?
"To Arataka -- From Mom"
"Save me! -- Kokkuri-san won't leave my house!"
"To Arataka -- From Mom" "Save me!
-- Kokkuri-san won't leave my house! "Exorcism request -- Hello? Are you a psychic?” "Perv Master -- We got a fresh batch of pervy..." "You're a fake -- I'll curse you... CurseCurseCurse" "Spirit photo -- I ended up taking one."
"To Reigen Arataka Happy birthday. How are you doing? How's work? Are
you still in that shady business? Remember our neighbors, the Kobayashis?
I heard their oldest son got married just last month. You should hurry up and find a secure job. You still have
a chance. You're still only 28. If you want another chance at life, you should probably make a decision fast...”
"Make sure you take care of yourself. Here's
my gift to you." "Open file attachment"
"Looking for staff" "Whitey Recruitment
Invitation" "A cheerful and fun workplace"
» Melt, melt, melt your brain with electronic waves )
Still training to get a real feel of it
--Are you having fun?
--» So all together now )
-- I think so?
--» Melancholy! )
You have no rhythm, do you, Mob-kun?
Yeah! Wahoo!
Correct.
"Reunion"
"Happy Trails"
Ooh, Arataka-chan!
Welcome. It's been too long.
Hey, it's Reigen-san! Reigen-sensei is here!
Sensei! Come sit over here, Sensei!
One lemon sour...
Extra on the sour.
Should you be drinking?
Yeah.
The regulars here are a bunch of people
who'd fall for pyramid schemes or fake cults.
People like that who want someone
to vent their troubles to
"Happy Trails"
relieve their stress at this bar.
Relieve their stress at this bar.
It's basically a gold mine
for someone like me.
It's a place where a bunch
of weak people gather.
Hear me out, Reigen-san!
The other day, this really
pretty girl talked to me.
When I followed her,
she led me to some art exhibit...
You were taken to an exhibit where a copy
of a famous painting was on display.
It's a dating scheme.
I'll hear them out and give them
some random words of advice.
Apparently, that's enough
for them to respect me.
Maybe they're... almost like friends to me.
It's... my birthday today.
Well, happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Sensei.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
This is the perfect time to bring
this up since it's your birthday!
I have this amazing pillow I got
from this extra special connection.
It's memory foam, so you'll sleep like a baby!
It's worth 120,000 yen, but...
Arataka-chan, this is your
first drink, isn't it?
Your face is all red. Are you all right?
Nope.
Wh-What's wrong?
Tab, please.
Well, that backfired.
I was thinking that I wanted
to talk to someone... anyone.
I guess I don't have any friends.
But I didn't even put any alcohol in it...
This situation's not good...
I'm going in a very bad direction.
Me, of all people!
Wait... Me?
I mean, what...
What...
What am I?
I guess I'm just going to have to...
...become somebody.
After ending up alone and getting over it,
Reigen made a huge change.
I, Reigen Arataka, shall accept this job!
"New Reigen Arataka"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
I, Reigen Arataka, shall accept this job!
"Spirits and Such
Consultation Office"
"Spirits and Such Consultation
Office" He started beautifying the city,
He started beautifying the city,
live-streamed exorcisms online,
"Don't tell people personal information they don't need to know. No
payments upfront. Don't sign any contracts. Vases I Holy water I Salt"
"Don't tell people personal information they don"t need to know. No payments upfront. Don't sign any
contracts. Vases I Holy water I Salt” held free seminars and even offered people life counseling,
held free seminars and even
offered people life counseling,
broadening his field of work.
"Noritama-san's Review" "'Spirits and Such Consultation Office' is wonderful. The man in charge, Reigen Arataka-san, is a
true psychic. Because of him, my body feels much lighter, and I can feel my luck improving."” broadening his field of work.
Broadening his field of work.
"Flat Tire-san's Review" "Reigen Arataka-san is one of the few real psychics. He listened to me,
gave me advice, and I finally met my match. Thank you so much.” broadening his field of work.
"Flat Tire-san's Review" "Reigen Arataka-san is one of the few real psychics. He
listened to me, gave me advice, and I finally met my match. Thank you so much.”
However, he continued to execute his
usual exorcism jobs with vigor.
"Stray Cat of the Dawn's Review" “"I'm so thankful that I just can"t stop crying. No one was willing to help me out,
but Reigen... I might just be falling in love..." However, he continued to execute his usual exorcism jobs with vigor.
However, he continued to execute his
usual exorcism jobs with vigor.
"All of our satisfied customers" However, he continued
to execute his usual exorcism jobs with vigor.
However, he continued to execute his
usual exorcism jobs with vigor.
Among his most recent jobs,
there was a rumor that the Player Killer
"Fantasy Hell" Among his most recent jobs,
"Fantasy Hell"
"Fantasy Hell" from the super-popular online
game, Fantasy Hell, was actually a ghost.
From the super-popular online game,
Fantasy Hell, was actually a ghost.
It was a difficult job that many
other psychics declined to take.
"We asked Shinra Banshomaru
what he thought"
I've heard of it, but don't even bother.
It's not something we can handle.
Our spiritual power can't
do anything inside a game.
Right?
Meaning it was a target that even
Mob wouldn't be able to exorcise.
However, Reigen used multiple accounts
and stayed up late many nights,
repeatedly leveling up and
strengthening his weapons...
He then baited the ghost
player and surrounded it,
then beat the crap out of him.
And then, finally,
he succeeded in the exorcism.
Y-You're amazing!
You actually exorcised him!
But how?
Well, I am a psychic...
Shit. I made too many in-game purchases,
and now I'm in the red...
Because of this successful job,
the agency's popularity continued to rise.
"Popularity”
"I Love Online Games@netgman Reigen Arataka is the real deal! He exorcised
the online ghost! #FantasyHell #SpiritsandSuchConsultationOffice”
"Popularity”
"The Online Ghost Has Finally Been Exorcised!
A True Psychic Actually Exists"
"The Online Ghost Has Finally Been Exorcised! A True
Psychic Actually Exists" Someone eventually started
Someone eventually started
"Popularity”
calling Reigen "the Bro of Seasoning City,"
"Reigen Arataka Fansite A Blog About 'the Bro of Seasoning City' This site is about the
'Spirits and Such Consultation Office'..." calling Reigen "the Bro of Seasoning City,"
calling Reigen "the Bro of Seasoning City,"
"Popularity”
"Reigen Arataka... There's no doubt about it... The man might
seriously be a god." and his popularity skyrocketed so much,
and his popularity skyrocketed so much,
"Popularity”
he even got interviewed for a magazine.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
And a few days after that...
"Gozz TV Director Binwan Taro"
TV!
You mean I'm that popular?
One of our producers happened to hear
about you and wanted you on our show.
"Supernatural Detective! Do Spiritual Powers Actually Exist? Special” One
of our producers happened to hear about you and wanted you on our show.
"Supernatural Detective! Do Spiritual
Powers Actually Exist? Special”
"Supernatural Detective! Do Spiritual Powers
Actually Exist? Special” A national broadcast?
"Supernatural Detective! Do Spiritual
Powers Actually Exist? Special”
If you manage to get popular on TV,
you'll immediately shoot to
the top of the psychic world.
"One week later"
Supernatural Detective...
Do Spiritual Powers Actually Exist? Special!
"Supernatural Detective Specia!!!" Do
Spiritual Powers Actually Exist? Special!
"Supernatural Detective
Specia!!!"
We are live tonight!
"Host Ebihara Morizo" I,
Ebihara Morizo, am your host,
I, Ebihara Morizo, am your host,
"Mogi Tatsuya”
"Mogi Tatsuya” joined by our guests, sci-fi
researcher Mogi Tatsuya-san and idol SATAKE-san.
"Mogi Tatsuya”
"Mogi Tatsuya” --Thanks for having me.
--Hello!
--Thanks for having me.
"Jodo Kirin" "Reigen Arataka"
"Jodo Kirin" "Reigen Arataka" We also
have some psychics with us here today.
"Jodo Kirin" "Reigen Arataka"
It's a pleasure to have you on the program.
The pleasure's all mine.
"Jodo Kirin" "Reigen Arataka"
Holy crap... I'm actually on TV.
Everything's going so smoothly.
"Do Spiritual Powers Actually Exist!? Special!I” Today, we've
invited someone who claims to be possessed by an evil spirit.
"Do Spiritual Powers Actually Exist!?
Specia!!"!”
"Do Spiritual Powers Actually Exist!? Special!I” We
will have our experts exorcise them live on our program!
"Do Spiritual Powers Actually Exist!?
Specia!!!”
Come on, now...
If I actually pull this off like
a rock star on national TV,
maybe I'll get even more fans...
All right.
--1"'m nervous, but I'm going to show them what I've got!
--"...nervous, but I'm going to show them what I've got, "
is what you're thinking, isn't it?
That ego of yours is going to
deflate soon enough, you fool!
I'm the one who mentioned you to
one of the TV station's producers!
My disciples told me about
what happened that day!
"Anti-Possession Jumping Knee Strike"
"Anti-Possession Jumping Knee Strike" They told me how
you had the nerve to nail me with a jumping knee strike!
"Anti-Possession Jumping Knee Strike"
I'm going to make you pay dearly!
I'll make damn sure you
regret what you've done!
I spilled a seed and lost sight of it
I'll find it using the color it's dyed in
and watch it grow
It immediately returned
to the palm of my hand
But it's still too light and too frail
to reach for the skies
The world coldly drains away all the heat
The bright sunshine just isn't enough
The memories are closing off what lies ahead
Shake off their warmth
and set off into the distance
If I let it wither, it'd be over just like that
But my hope just doesn't fade away
The new star of the 21st
century, Reigen Arataka!
He makes his TV debut!
And on national TV!
I've finally come this far.
Just you watch, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 7:
"Cornered
- True Identity~."
"Cornered - True Identity~" The
Blu-rays? An even better decision.